relishapp.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy policy - Relish

This privacy policy sets out how Cucumber Limited uses and protects any information that you give Cucumber Limited when you use this website. 

Cucumber Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Cucumber Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 5 July 2012. 

##  What we collect 

When you sign up for an account, we collect the following information: 

  * Full legal name
  * Email address
  * Username (otherwise known as nickname or handle)

###  What we do with the information we gather 

We require this information to provide you with an identity on the website, to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Notifying you of events that have happened on projects you're collaborating on.
  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

##  Security 

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

##  How we use cookies 

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps us to recognise you automatically when you return to the site. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

We use cookies for a single purpose: to record your "Remember me" preference when signing in to your account 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

##  Links to other websites 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

##  Controlling your personal information 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [support@relishapp.com](mailto:support@relishapp.com)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
